famedstar.com 2019-04-30

# Privacy Policy - Famed Star

**Famedstar.com** to collect visitor data and analyze traffic on our site. This information helps us understand visitors interests and helps us improve our website. When you visit our site, the pages that you look at, and a short text file called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer/Mobile. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis only. The cookie does not contain personal details and you don’t have to worry about it. We does not sell or give the statistics they store to any 3rd parties for data-mining or marketing purposes.

 **General Data Protection Regulation [European and UK residents] :-**

  * The right to access your personal data
  * The right to correct your personal data if it is inaccurate, expired or outdated.
  * You are allowed to be removal or erase of your personal data we will removal or erase your data as soon as possible.
  * You are allowed to be informed about personal data we collect and how we process it

 **Security Factor :-**

  * We scan our server regularly.
  * We use only verified and certified plug-in such as Jetpack, Yoast, Tablepress etc.
  * We do not use cookies for tracking or marketing purposes.
  * We use Jetpack which is a web analytics service that helps us to track our visitors and improve the website for the best possible user experience.
  * We use spam filtering Third-party service “Akismet”, which checked the visitors comments and filtered the spam comments.
  * We also using Content Delivery Network [MaxCDN], which protect your data with several layers of protection mechanisms like Firewalls, Two-factor authentication, Whitelists etc.

 **Advertisement :-**

  * We use only Google AdSense as an advertising medium for “Famedstar.com”. Google AdSense uses cookies as a medium to sort out your interest and serves ads on the basis of your most recent visits.

 **Contact Information :-**

  * You simply visit our “Contact US” page for any query or suggestion for regarding Privacy policies.
